Don't blow it.
Whistle is a horror, mystery film directed by Corin Hardy.
When a group of misfit teenagers stumble upon an ancient Aztec death whistle, they learn that by
blowing it, its terrifying sound will invoke their future deaths to hunt them down.
As the body count rises, the friends investigate the origins of the deadly artifact in a
desperate effort to stop the horrifying chain of events that they've set in motion.
Chrys Willet, played by Dafne Keen.
Ellie Gains, played by Sophie Nélisse.
Rel, played by Sky Yang.
Dean, played by Jhaleil Swaby.
Grace Friedkin, played by Alissa Skovbye.
Noah Haggerty, played by Percy Hynes White.
Whistle is a 2025 horror film directed by Corin
Hardy and written by Owen Egerton.
It stars Dafne Keen, Sophie Nélisse, Sky Yang, Jhaleil Swaby, Ali
Skovbye, Percy Hynes White, Michelle Fairley and Nick Frost.
The film premiered at Fantastic Fest on 25 September 2025.
The film explores themes of high school, evil spirit, school, death, whistle.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.